Contact

amberrader0414@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amber-rader-msn-rn-wcc-06881691 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Healthcare Management Hospitals

Amber Rader, MSN, RN, WCC

Travel Nurse at Assured Nursing Inc

Indianapolis, Indiana Area

Summary

I've been a nurse for about 13 years. I finish my FNP program at Duquesne University at the end of July. I am Wound Care Certified. I adapt well to change, love learning, and new challenges. I strive to provide the highest quality patient care every day. I have many skill sets and learn new tasks quickly.

Experience

Assured Nursing Inc Travel Nurse December 2019 - Present (7 months)

St.Vincent Indianapolis Hospital
PCCU RN
September 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 4 months)
Indianapolis, Indiana

Community Nursing & Rehabilitation Center Wound Nurse April 2018 - September 2018 (6 months) Indianapolis, Indiana

Stonebrooke Rehabilitation Centre Director Of Nursing November 2016 - April 2018 (1 year 6 months) New Castle, IN

Our Hospice of South Central Indiana Hospice June 2016 - December 2016 (7 months)

American Senior Communities 8 years 7 months Registered Nurse June 2010 - May 2016 (6 years)
Unit Manager, ADNS, MDS, DNS

Licensed Practical Nurse November 2007 - June 2010 (2 years 8 months)

Education

Duquesne University School of Nursing Family Nurse Practitioner, Nursing (2018 - 2020)

Western Governors University

Master's Degree, Nursing Leadership & Management · (2016 - 2018)

Western Governors University
Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2016)

Ivy Tech Community College
ASN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2010)

Ivy Tech Community College
Technical Certificate, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse
Training · (2005 - 2007)